I hate television. Gets me headaches.
我讨厌电视,让我头疼
You know there are so many magnetic waves, travel in the airspace because of TV and television
电视产生许多的电磁波
We are losing 10 times as many brain cells as we're supposed to.
会造成10倍的脑细胞受损
oh, please
噢,拜托
The cow says blake, three letters
母牛大叫的声音,三个字
Dude.
公子哥
Dude, I don't know
公子哥,我不懂...
Magnetic waves, brain cells, I don't understand the connections between all that stuff.
电磁波、脑细胞之间有什么关连?
You know what else I heard, the magnetic waves shrink silicone molecules.
我还听说,电磁波会使矽分子萎缩
Oh my god, turn it off.
天啊,关掉它
It's not working.
关不掉
It's backwards.
见鬼啦
What do I do?
我该怎么做?
I don't know.
我不晓得
That was kind of scary.
真吓人
I know something even scarier.
我听过更吓人的事
What?
什么事?
Have you heard about this video tape?
你听过有关录影带的事吗?
The one where they do it on the boat
是在船上拍摄的
and then in the car, and then in the bathtub
之后在车内,然后在浴缸
and he's like “Hey baby, I love you.”
他说:嘿!宝贝,我爱你
And she's like “where are we”
而她说:我们在哪?
And did you see the size... - No! Not that tape.
-你知道那... -不!不是那种
The one with all the scary images
有很多恐怖的画面
and after you watch the tape, the phone rings,
你看了录影带之后,电话响起
there's a really scary voice comes on, says you gonna die in like...
就会有恐怖的声音传来 说你会死于...
Seven days? Yeah, I saw that one with Josh last weekend.
七天内? 是呀,上周末我和乔许看过
You were with Josh last weekend? Oh my God.
上周末你和乔许? 我的天啊
Oh yes I was.
我和他一起看的
Oh you asshole
你这个混蛋
You know it
看招
This is realy weird.
真是奇怪
Yeah, big house only one phone.
对呀,这么大的房子只有一支电话
Hello?
喂?
I am coming for you, my precious.
我正要找你,宝贝
Hi Mom.
嗨,妈
Hi precious, having fun?
嗨,宝贝,开心吗?
Yes, ask your Mom which bathroom has the vibrating showerhead?
问问你妈 浴室有没有会振动的莲蓬头?
What?
什么?
Hello?
喂?
Katie? Katie
凯蒂? 凯蒂
Katie?
凯蒂?
Are you OK?
你没事吧?
你还好吧?
Scary Movie 3
《惊声尖笑３》
20 miles west of Washington D.C.
华盛顿特区以西20哩
God!
天啊!
Tom, did you hear...?
-汤姆,你听到...? -嘘
The dogs are acting strange.
狗儿们的举动异常
Damn it
妈的
Sue
苏
What are you doing out here?
你在这里干什么?
You're really sick
你真的病了
What's wrong?
怎么了?
I wonder what they're trying to tell us.
我猜他们想告诉我们些什么
"Attack here"
"攻击这里"
And now, Washington DC's leading morning news program, the Morning News.
现在报导华盛顿特区的晨间新闻
Good morning, I'm Ross Giggins.
早安,我是罗斯吉更
For our top story we turn now to Cindy Campbell.
首则新闻现在交给辛蒂坎波
Thank you Ross.
谢谢罗斯
There's a developing story in Middleburg in this hour
稍早,米多柏格发生了一件事
A mystery crop circle appeared in local farmer Tom Logan's corn field.
一个谜样的农作物景象 出现在当地农夫汤姆的玉米田里
Eloborate prank or extraterrestrial phenomenon?
是精心制作的恶作剧 或是外星人所为?
We'll update you as soon as we have any further information.
有更进一步的消息 我们会立刻为你报导
But either way, it's clear that something strange is happening in that small town.
另一方面 该小镇也发生了奇怪的事
Ross?
罗斯?
I'm sorry, I wasn't listening.
抱歉,我没注意听
Coming up, more news after this.
接下来,会有更多的新闻
Cindy you got a second? -Sure.
-辛蒂,有空吗? -当然
I want you to take a look at this for that big strip club expose.
我希望你去揭穿大型脱衣舞厅
I'd rather stick with the crop circle story.
我相当注意这件农作物案
Oh come on, you know those things are just a hoax.
拜托,那只是场恶作剧
No! I'm telling you I'm sensitive about that corn field
不!我对玉米田的事很敏锐的
call it women's intuition, or ESPN, or both,
这叫作女人的直觉或者是第六感
but I can tell when danger is near, I just...
当危险接近时,我可以告诉你 我...
Cindy, it's sweeps month.
辛蒂,现在是扫荡月
Rating means everything.
收视率代表一切
People want human interests story, like the one you did yesterday.
大众想看有趣的报导 就像你昨天报的那种
The report on breast documentation?
报导内容着重在胸部?
That was just ten minutes of topless women.
就只要10分钟的上空女人
I mean, come on
我是说,来吧
Why these are so interesting, oh for god's sake
为什么对这样的事那么有兴趣?
People don't care about this.
大众才不管这些呢
They want hard-hitting stories, indepth coverage and ...
大众想看扎实的故事 深入的报导,还有...
And twins
双胞姐妹花
You think it was the boys who cut that stuff in your corn?
你觉得玉米田景象是人为的吗?
All I know is my crops are gone.
我只知道我的农作物不见了
The bank's gonna close if I can't pay the rent.
付不出租金,田地就完了
I got 60 days to come up with all the fifty
60天内我得交出全部的50%
I'm sorry, the last thing you need was...
抱歉,最后一件事,你必须...
hardship in your life.
辛苦一辈子
Especially after what happen to you
特别在遭逢巨变之后
Sheriff, I don't need your sympathy
警官,我不需要你的同情
I didn't mean to upset you Father.
神父,我也不想让你难过
Please, I'm not a minister anymore
拜托,我不再是牧师了
I lost my faith.
我已丧失信心
A terrible night.
可怕的一夜
Your faith will return, just as sure as the sun will rise.
只要太阳升起,你的信心会回来的
That sounds like a long shot.
听起来遥不可及
Look, there is always an explanation for all this so-called phenomenon
这种现象总是有原因的
Maybe you are right. It's probally just the weasels
或许你说的对,可能是黄鼠狼
And when I get through with them, I doubt you will be seeing anything strange on this farm for a long time
当我逮到他们,农场就不会有怪事
We'll see.
等着瞧
You alright Tom? Get some rest.
汤姆,你没事吧? 好好休息
George!
乔治!
I need you back here tomorrow night after you pick up Sue.
明天接完苏以后,晚上就回来这里
That tracktor needs fixing.
牵引机需要修理
Sorry dog, I can't help you.
抱歉,我无法帮你
I have to get ready for my show.
我必须准备我的表演
Not that stupid hip hop stuff again
不会又是无聊的嘻哈玩意吧?
Damn it, Geogre, when are you gonna do something with your life?
可恶,你何时才会有所作为?
I've got a dream!
我有个梦想!
What is your dream?
你的梦想是什么?
To have a dream
拥有梦想
Geogre, all you've done is chase adolescence fantasies.
乔治,你追求的只是青春期的幻想
I wanna be an astronaut.  A cowboy. Gynaecologist of the stars.
我想当太空人、牛仔、名医师
And now, the stupid hip hop thing.
而现在,这是无聊的嘻哈事
For your information, this stupid hip hop thing is gonna get me paid.
照你的说法,嘻哈事能让我赚钱
I'm gonna win that rap battle tomorrow night.
明晚,我将取得饶舌战的胜利
Rap battle? Oh for god's sake.
饶舌战? 天哪
You just hate me cause I'm black.
你讨厌我,因为我是黑人
You don't have any faith in me, you don't have any faith in anything anymore.
你对我没有任何信心 你对任何事都没有信心
So why don't you just worry about you, and I will worry about...
你担心你自己就好,而我担心...
Cody.
柯迪
You're late again, Cindy.
辛蒂,你又迟到了
I'm sorry, I was stuck in traffic.
对不起,交通堵塞
Cindy!
辛蒂!
Brenda, hi!
嗨,布兰达!
It's great to see you.
能看到你真是太好了
It's been so long...
已经好久了...
Oh, too long,
噢,好久了
I've been working so hard
我忙于工作
You know I had to spent more and more time at the station
我必须花越来越多的时间在电视台
And the news just keeps coming in.
而新闻节目才稳住收视率
What was the assignment?
作业是什么?
Draw your family and friends. - Oh
-画家人和朋友 -噢
So...anyone new in your life, Cindy?
嗯...辛蒂,有没有男朋友了?
No. You know I just don't feel the right guy.
没有,我还没碰到真命天子
I'm looking for something more than just good sex.
我要的不只是性爱
I know,  you want commitment.
我知道,你想托付终身
No, I want great sex. And what I mean by...
不,我想要伟大的性爱 我的意思是...
That's what I'm talking about.
那正是我想说的
You want a guy that's like bang bang bang
你要勇猛耐操的男人
You know what I'm saying?
你懂我说的吧?
Did I say stop drawing?
我有说停止画画吗?
Look, when I mean Mr. Right, I don't know
当我遇到真命天子时,我不知道...
Uncle George!
乔治叔叔!
Hey, sweetie. Come here!
嘿,甜心,过来!
How are you?
你好吗?
Go get your stuff, ok?
去拿你的东西,好吗?
I know you, you are Tom Logan's brother.
我认识你,你是汤姆罗根的弟弟
And you are that reporter Cindy Campbell.
你是记者辛蒂坎波
You did the story on our cop cycles.
你报导我们的农作物回圈
Crop circles.
农作物圆圈
Right
没错
So...you are here to pick up your...
那...你是来接你的...
...nephew. Cody.
...侄子,柯迪
You don't dress like a farmer.
你穿着不像农夫
My brother is the farmer, I'm the rapper.
我哥哥是农夫,我是饶舌歌手
Oh for real.
事实上
And here is the 611 on that.
这里是611
That's phone repair, you mean 411.
电话送修了,你是说411吧
Right. So, I will be doing my rap battle at the 23 club tomorrow night
对,明晚在23俱乐部 我有场饶舌大战
I don't believe this shit.
我不信那玩意儿
You two should come down!
你们两个要冷静!
I'll be rapping, I'll be capping, I'll be tapping, I'll be flapping, I'll be happe...ning.
我要饶舌、我要叩叩、我要敲敲 我要拍拍,我要快乐...颂
Ding bing wing, yo
丁、兵、赢
Sounds good
听起来不赖
Would, could, should, hood
吴、古、苏、胡
Oh if we say we will come, will you shut you ass up?
如果我们说会去,你会闭嘴吗?
Ok then, fresh, I will see you guys tomorrow night.
那好,新鲜人,明晚见
Ok bye.
好,再见
Peace out.
再见
Now who the fuck did that?
谁干的?
Honey what is it?
甜心,怎么了?
Are you having one of your visions?
是不是看见了什么现象?
There is a girl with black hair.
有个黑头发的女孩
She wants to kill you.
她想杀你
Your period starts in three, two, one
你的经期到了,三、二、一
Ho, what else? Cody what else do you see?
还有呢?柯迪,你还看到什么?
I see a little boy, and a grown woman but no father.
我看见一个小男孩 和一个没父亲的成年女人
Oh Cody
噢,柯迪
I see you are kneeling in dog shit.
我看见你跪在狗屎上
What?
什么?
Oh for god's sake.
噢,天哪
Cody, don't you understand?
柯迪,你不明白吗?
As long as we have each other that's all we need.
我们只要有对方就够了
Cody, I know things have been tough since your mom died.
柯迪,我知道自从你母亲去世 你就过得很辛苦
God, I've been so selfish
我这么地自私
I was putting my career first From now on. I'm gonna be thinking about you, 24/7.
总是把自己的事业摆第一 从现在起,我会天天关心你
Damn
该死
Wait Cindy.
等等我,辛蒂
Honey, I'm gonna be leaving soon. So...
甜心,我待会要离开,所以...
Do you know who she is?
认得她是谁吗?
No, but sometimes she talks to me
不认识,但有时候她跟我说话
She's coming tonight.
她今晚会来
Oh, Father Muldoon.
噢,马杜神父
Cindy
辛蒂
I'm so glad you can come.
很高兴你能来
We've called all over for baby-sitters
我们到处在找褓姆
I don't mind filling in now and then, where is little Cody?
偶尔来帮忙,我不介意 小柯迪在哪?
I don't know, he must be back in his room, playing.
不晓得,他大概是回房去玩了
Anyway, I left a number where I can be reached on the table
总之,桌上留有电话号码
Also he has a little rush on his behind.
还有,他屁股有红疹
So make sure he takes a bath
记得叫他洗澡
Thank you father, good night
谢谢你,神父,晚安
Cody?
柯迪?
Yeah yeah, yeah, check over here
耶耶耶,照过来
Hey, look, before we get on with the battle tonight,
注意,在今晚开战之前
I've got a couple of announcement to make.
我有些事情宣布
I know y'all don't wanna bust a cap in the air for your favourite battle
我知道你们都不愿见到场面搞砸了
but if you could please hold on to your gunfire until the end of the show
请你们到节目最后 再表示你们的热情
Now look, let's just put the safe on
听着,大家把保险关上...
It's on the left side of the gun above the trigger guard
它在枪的左边、扳机的上面
Can somebody get his ass out of here? Get his ass out of here
有没有人能让他滚出去? 让他滚出去
Alright, DJ, spin that shit.
好的,DJ,樵落去
Wow, my bad - Motherf...
-哇,失礼 -去你妈...
Brenda, something wrong? You look scared.
布兰达,有事吗?你看起来很害怕
I don't know, all that stuff I was seeing on TV
我不晓得,我曾在电视上看到过
I just got a weird feeling that something bad is heading my way like...
当你在车后面看到亚洲人...
when you see an Asian person behind the wheel of a car
我觉得有不好的事要发生
Cindy, after the show you think maybe you can come back to my crib and hang out with me?
辛蒂,节目结束后,你能到我家吗?
I don't wanna be alone.
我不想孤单一个人
Oh of course I will, Brenda.
当然可以,布兰达
Oh, I love you
喔,我爱你
Pay my way, OK?
让我先走,好吗?
Yo yo yo, George, what's up?
唷...,乔治,怎么样?
What a man with the title of rapper, on the street baby That's good, it's good baby
好一个街头饶舌王,太好了,好小子
Finally, the white man is gonna screw the black man on harder rap
白人总算要教训黑人怎样饶舌
Yeah, I guess. How many people here you think?
我想是吧,你认为这里有多少人?
I don't know, man.
我不清楚
A 100, 200 whitey hating cron packing wait for your whitey ass bringing that shit.
一、二百个白人等着你去痛宰他们
Yes, at least.
没错,至少有这么多
what's wrong George?
怎么了,乔治?
You ever wonder when it's time to stop living up here
你曾经想知道何时不住在上面
and start living down here?
然后开始住在下面吗?
But what if we stop living over here
可是,如果我们不住这里
and move over there?
要搬到那里?
Shit. My aunt Shaneequa lives over there. ??? man.
胡扯,我阿姨夏妮就住那里
Where? What for? - Mice
-哪里? 干嘛? -老鼠
Mice, I thought she had rats.
老鼠,我想她有家鼠
No,  rats are outside, mice are inside.
不,老鼠在外面,家鼠在里面
Yo, but what if a mouse goes outside, it become a rat
家鼠出去变老鼠
and if there is a rat in the house, it is a mouse.
进到屋里变家鼠
I don't see no mouse outside. That's what I'm saying.
我没看过外面有老鼠的
That's because it's a rat. Fool
那是因为它是家鼠,傻瓜
You might just make a fact That is the real shit
你只会造成一个事实 那就是瞎掰
Fellows, what you guys talking about?
两位,你们在说些什么?
Yo, George, you need some? I will do anything for you, anything.
乔治,你需要什么吗? 我愿意为你做任何事,任何事
Well, about those cron packing whitey hating gangsters, perhaps you
关于那些白人痛恨帮派份子 也许你...
What he needs is a hype, man
也许他需要一点刺激
Yeah, yeah, come on,
对,没错,来吧
You can be his bliss store
你可以祝福他
That's me, that's what I do
没错,那就是我要做的
That's my job, baby! That's what I do, you know
那是我的工作,宝贝! 那就是我要做的
That's what I do. Yo, hype man, you take them hits
那就是我要做的,猛男 给他们迎头痛击
Let's get outta there, man
出马上阵吧,兄弟
Hey, the tail boy what it's gonna be
嘿,菜鸟男孩会是什么样子
You cannot escape you're fake in the streets.
你不能逃避,你是个街头骗子
Okay, I count cash, you count shit
唷,你数大便,我数钞票
Better not sleep when a beast competes you
和野兽比赛,千万不要睡觉
Alright, alright, alright. That was hot That was what I'm talking about.
很好...,真够呛,我要说的就是...
That was hot, right, right?
真够呛,对吗,对吗?
Yo, yo, what do ya think?
喂,你怎么认为?
I thought they were both absolutely dreadful.
我认为他们俩都很烂
??? - What?
-不入流? -什么?
I don't know what I'm doing here.
我搞不懂我在这里干嘛
This club is totally pathetic.
这个俱乐部太可悲了
Everybody, put your hands...
各位,举起你的手...
This is it, you're ready, Geogre? The show time baby. - OK
-准备好了吗,乔治? 好戏上场了 -好
Just wanna let you know, man, that no matter what goes on that stage tonight
我只想让你知道 不论今晚舞台发生什么事
gonna always be in my heart. - Oh, that's love, that's love right there
-你都永远在我的心中 -这就是爱,爱就在心中
I love you - That's what I'm talking about
-我爱你 -这就是我要说的
Look, man. Can you feel it, can you feel my love when you're here?
兄弟,感觉到了吗? 此刻你感受到我的爱了吗?
OK, come on you go out there rap it tonight, alright man?
好了,今晚上台饶舌一番,行不行?
Alright, alright, we gon' bring you
没问题,很好,我们支持你
Let's go baby, you are hot
我们上,你够呛
Yeah, alright, alright,  you're ready for the next roller
耶,很好,很好 你们准备好下一场了吗?
To my left, we have the ringing champion.
在我左手边,是响铃冠军
BX111
BX 111
Some of ya call him Jealous Ones Still Envy
有人说他是嫉妒之王
Some of ya call him Don Cartegena
有人叫他西班牙卡提吉那
Some of y'all call him Joey Crack
有人称他为爆裂乔伊
Stick 'em up
顶爆你
But tonight, let's give it up for Fat Joe!
今晚,让我们欢迎胖子乔!
I gotta go get him?!
我要跟他对干?!
Give it up.
大声点
What ???  Fat Joe
只不过是胖子乔罢了
Joe, Joe, Joe
乔、乔、乔
??? say, go go go
管他说什么,上...
Now the challenge
现在介绍挑战者
He's a farmer rapper so you know he's been kicking the shit all day
他是农场饶舌高手 他一天到晚呛声
Let's give it up for my man, George.
让我们大声喊他出来,乔治
Talking back, yeah, yeah
顶回去,耶,耶
That's right, I'll take Joey Crack
这就对了,爆裂乔伊
You win the champion, so you get to spit first. Your DJ
你是冠军,你先来
Spin that shit
DJ,樵落去
This guy can't be serious right here.
这家伙不能板着脸站在这里
Standing mini me AKA. I hope he ain't the guy you fight with.
站在我面前,简直不能比 希望他不是跟你打架的俗辣
Hey, yo, let's stick this man. cause he ain't got no skills, cause
嘿,唷,让这家伙杵在这里 因为他没任何本领
He's a white but he's not real.
因为他是白人却又不够纯
I hurt your feeling but you never gonna do, dog
我伤了你根本就没有的感觉
He's a white but he's not real
他是白人却又不够纯
You will need to win that hay stack but dumb.
你只能赢不会讲话的草堆
The city slicker forgive cows look your mom's titty slicker, but he lives
这个老妈都不原谅苟活的城市骗子
but he wasn't end up to have kids with his cousin.
居然跟表妹搞出孩子
Haven't thought my number one fan would be like dededede
想不到我的头号歌迷都唱...
that means Fat Joe is the man, and you are the liar in denial
胖子乔是条汉子,别否认你是骗子
Kill your whack quicker and then die in empire
敢随便呛声,死得更快
How dare you want to just with me.
你好大胆子敢跟我比赛
Looking like you've done the source of the mad cow disease, you're fake D-rabbit
你看来就像狂牛病的来源 你是冒牌的低级兔子
I don't mean 8 miles down the road the fogs the tatoo win.
我没说你是街头痞子 但就算乌龟迷路,一样会赢
OK, don't go, wait a minute
好胆别走,等一下
Alright, alright , that was hot. That was tight, Fat Joe.
好,好,真够呛,够厉害,胖子乔
Yo, now everybody give it up for my man George.
现在请大家为我兄弟乔治大声加油
DJ, spin the shit
DJ,樵落去
Bitch
贱人
Hoe
锄头
Now everybody in the 202, throw your hands in the air 'cause Fat Joe is through
现场202的每个人挥舞你的双手 因为胖子乔就要玩完
Now everybody in the 202, throw 'em up! Check it out - Go, go, go
现场202的每个人挥挥手!听好来
I'm a white boy, but my neck is red
我是白人,但我的脖子是红色
I put miracle whip on my wonder bread
就算我的面包可以打人也别奇怪
My face is pale, and I ain't ever been in jail
我脸色苍白,但没进过监牢
Me and buddies spend every winter in Vale
我和伙伴每个冬天都在一起
How many bitches have I slapped? Zero. Uh!
我打过几个贱人的巴掌? 没半个!
And Martha Stewart happens to be my hero
马沙史都华是我的英雄
I grew up on a farm and I was born with no rhythm
我在农场成长,天生没有节奏感
Dr. Phil's my uncle and I like to hang with him
我叔叔费尔博士,我常跟他相处
I can't dance, I wear khaki pants
我不会跳舞,我穿卡其短裤
My middle name's Lance
我中间的名字叫兰斯
My Grandma's from France So maybe I'm whack
我外婆来自法国,也许我是黑人
'Cause my skin ain't black
因为我的皮肤不是黑的
But you can't talk smack
看你还有什么好说的
'Cause whitey just struck back
因为白人刚刚还击
That's what I talk about!
那就是我要说的!
Give it up for George
给乔治一点鼓励
That's rap boy right there Oh shit, oh
饶舌男孩在这里,噢,糟糕
George, George, lose the hood
乔治,乔治,把风衣帽拿掉
I know we are in the hood now.
我知道我戴着帽子
No, man
别这样
He's a dead man.
他真该死
You guys feel me? In the hood?
你们感觉到了吗? 在风衣帽里?
I said, I'm done
我已经完了
Oh man, you can't give up rap just like that
兄弟,你不能那样就放弃饶舌
Rap? Shmap
饶舌? 嘘声吧
oh, look, you still got it, you see
听好,你还是可以的,了吧
Thanks for coming over tonight Cindy.
谢谢你今晚过来,辛蒂
I guess I'm just going though a rough time.
我正经历一段痛苦的日子
Brenda?	You wanna tell me what's really bothering you?
布兰达,想说出真正困扰你的事吗?
Well, there's something I need to... I saw a tape
有些事我需要...我看过一卷带子
I think you should know about it.
我觉得你应该知道
It had these really shocking images thing.
里面的画面真吓人
Brenda, it was Mardi Gras, I never drink vodka before.
布兰达,这是马迪格拉斯 我以前从未喝过伏特加酒
It was never out of beeds
它也没起过泡
No, not that tape Cindy
不,不是那个意思,辛蒂
Like just as in Urban Legend
就像在城市里传说的一样
You watch it, and as soon as it's over your phone rings
一旦你看了它,你的电话就会响起
and a creepy voice says: you gonna die in 7 days.
然后一个可怕的声音说: 七天内,你就要死了
And 7 days later...
七天之后...
When did you watch it?
你什么时候看的?
A week ago, a week ago, tonight.
一星期前,一星期前的今晚
Brenda
布兰达
Oh my god
天哪
oh my god, you bitch
天啊,你这个贱人
Ketchup.
吓到你了
You should've seen the look on your face.
你应该看看你的表情
You got me.
你吓死我了
Brenda?
布兰达?
I can't believe that you fell for that fake seisure.
假装的痉挛你也上当
But it seem so real!!
可是看起来像真的!
Indeed, didn't it?
像真的,不是吗?
And you peed
你撒尿了
Yeah, I really thought I actually did that.
是啊,我真的认为我做到了
I just like that look on your face when you are scared. Girl, you are so easy!
我喜欢看你害怕的样子 你太好骗了
I got you with the old fake hand
用假手就骗到你了
Girl, you were scared.
你被吓到了
Well, I know.
我知道
Oh come on, I was just kidding.
拜托,我不过是开玩笑
But you've taken it too far Brenda.
但是你太过份了,布兰达
I'm gonna go get the rest of popcorn.
我要去拿剩下的爆米花
Cindy?
辛蒂?
Oh forget it, I'm not falling for it again.
少来了,我不会再上当的
Oh, come on!! Cindy, the news is on.
噢,拜托! 辛蒂,新闻开始了
Another little white girl that fell down a well
又一个小女孩掉进井里
Fifty black people get their asses beaten by police today
今天有五十个黑人被警察打
but the whole world gotta stop for one little whitey down a hole.
全世界将阻止一个小白人挖洞
Cindy, the TV is leaking.
辛蒂,电视在漏水
Cindy, Cindy, something is wrong here.
辛蒂,辛蒂,有问题
Cindy, this bitch is messing up my floor.
辛蒂,这个贱人把我的地板弄脏了
Cindy, help me!
辛蒂,救命!
I'm not listening.
我没在听
Get up you ugly bitch, come on, let me see what you got!
起来,你这丑贱人 来,让我看看你的本事!
What you got?! That's all?!
你有什么本事?! 就这么点?!
I'm whacking her ass,   Cindy.
我打得她屁滚尿流,辛蒂
Yeah, what's that.
耶,怎么样?
Cindy, please, help me. Cindy
辛蒂,救我,辛蒂
Ok, hang on a second.
好,等一下
Hello.
喂
Father Muldoon here, we're getting along famously.
我是马杜神父,我们相处地很融洽
thanks again, father, byebye.
再次感谢你,神父,再见
Brenda? Brenda?
布兰达?布兰达?
Brenda.
布兰达
Oh my god, yes, yes of course I will tell her. Thank you.
天哪,是,当然,我会转告她,谢谢
Sue's teacher Brenda, she's... she's dead.
苏的老师,布兰达 她...她死了
I better tell her.
我来跟她说
No no no, I can do it.
不...,让我来
Sue - Yes?
-苏 -什么事?
You know your teacher Miss Brenda?
你知道你的老师,布兰达小姐吗?
Yeah?
怎么了?
SHE'S dead
她死了
Gone forever, died horrible painful death.
她死得好惨、好痛苦
Gone gone gone just like your dog.
就像你的狗一样
My dog's dead?
我的狗死了?
I just ran him over with the car when I drove in
当我开车进来时,正好压到
everyone you love around you is dying
你周遭所爱的都死了
Hello Father.
你好,神父
Don't call me father.
别叫我神父
I am not a clergy-man since...
我没当牧师很久了...
I'm sorry about that night.
那晚的事,我很抱歉
If I hadn't fallen asleep, or driving for that exact 20 mins.
如果我没有睡着 或者准20分钟开车
If I hadn't drunk that exact whole bottle of Jagermeister.
如果我没喝下整瓶的贾格麦斯特
If only I hadn't killed that hooker - Simon, Simon
-如果我没有杀那小偷 -赛门,赛门
I don't see what any of this has to do with Annie
我不明白这些和安妮有什么关系
I'm sorry, those are other nights.
对不起,那是另外的夜晚
But if it had been that night, I might have missed her that terrible night.
可是如果在那天晚上 那可怕的夜晚,我可能会失去她
It's your wife, Father.She's hurt
是你太太,神父,她受伤了
Annie?
安妮?
She was hit by a truck and she's pinned against a tree.
她被卡车撞到,然后夹在树上
I don't understand.
我不明白
As long as the truck has her pinned, she will stay alive.
只要卡车将她撞倒,她就不会死
I still don't get it.
我还是不明白
This is your wife.
这是你的妻子
She broke her weiner?
她的腰断了?
Look what happens to the taco.
看这墨西哥夹饼的下场
Look, I don't understand all these fancy medical lingo I wannt see Annie.
我不明白这些难懂的医学术语 我只想见安妮
She's split in half.
她被分成两半
You mean, like down the middle in half.
你是说,从中间分一半?
At the waist.
从腰部
You mean this is the last time I can talk to the top half?
你是说,这是我和上半身说话 最后一次的机会?
Yes, the track is the only thing that is holding her together.
对,卡车是唯一把她夹住的东西
Let's say this is her bottom half, can I squeeze a few minutes with that?
如果这是她的下半身 我能抱几分钟吗?
I'm not sure what you mean…
我不明白你的意思
let me explain.
让我来解释...
Tom, go to her.
汤姆,去看她
Tom, I need a ride home!
汤姆,我需要有人带我回家!
Hey baby, how's going?
宝贝,怎么了?
Oh, I'm dying Tom.
我要死了,汤姆
Don't talk like that, the truck barely hit you.
别这么说,卡车几乎没碰到你
Honey, kiss me one last time.
甜心,再亲我最后一次
Promise me you will never re-marry
发誓你不再娶
I promise.
我发誓
And no sex either.
也不准做爱
I'm sorry, I didn't catch that.
对不起,我没听清楚
And no sex.
不准做爱
Honey, you're not speaking clearly. Your injury must be awful.
甜心,你说话不清楚了 你的伤一定很吓人
No sex!! - Oh, cruel fate destroys my life
-不准做爱! -噢,残酷的命运毁了我的人生
No sex! - Alright, honey, you hardly knew her, she'll be missed terribly
-不准做爱! -好了,甜心,你又不可能认识她
oh, jesus. - That's right honey, go into the light.
-噢,天哪 -对了,甜心,朝着光走
Look, just tell George swing away.
听好,叫乔治让开
Right, swing away.
好,让开
Oh sure.
当然
That you understand.
这个你就听得懂
Annie, Annie
安妮?安妮!
I'm sorry dude.
对不起,公子哥
Don't call me Dude, I'm not a stoner anymore. Not since...
别叫我公子哥,我已经不是了 打从那时候就不是...
Goodbye, Tom.
再见,汤姆
I'm so sorry Mr. and Mrs. Meeks.
很对不起,米克斯夫妇
Brenda was a good firend. When she was alive.
当她在世的时候 布兰达是很好的朋友
My sweet sweet Brenda, she look so peaceful.
甜甜的布兰达,她样子看来很平静
If only God had taken us instead of our daughter.
但愿上帝带走我们,而不是布兰达
I knew you knew Brenda like I did
我明白你们的心情 相信布兰达也跟我一样
I think she wishes the same thing.
想着同样的事
These just get in today, photos from her trip she took
这些是今天收到的 是她旅行时拍的照片
They're blank
是空白的
Turn them around, honey
翻个面
Oh, yes of course.
是的,当然
Who's this?
这是谁?
That's Ralph, he's right over there.
这是拉夫,他就在那边
Cody?
柯迪?
It's a boy, he's going to be an asshole.
是男孩,他将会是个混蛋
Smoke all you want, you're gonna be hit by a bus.
尽管抽吧,你会被巴士撞到
That's not fooling anyone.
你骗不了人的
Cindy  - George. - Hey
-辛蒂 -乔治
Sue wants to pay her respect to her teacher, you?
苏想来向老师致敬,你呢?
Brenda was my bitch.
布兰达是我的朋友
Of course.
当然
Are you ok?
你没事吧?
It's just an open coffin. I can't believe they just leave it out here like this.
只不过是口棺材 他们怎么让她这样躺在这里
George, it's a wake.
乔治,是守灵
Awake? Brenda, I saw miracle, I thought you were dead.
醒的? 布兰达,我见过奇迹 我以为你死了
Sue, your teacher's alive. Hello?
苏,你的老师还活着,哈?
I got your back George, I got your back.
我来帮你,乔治,我来帮你了
She's alive. Brenda
她还活着,布兰达
George, stop! She's dead
乔治,住手! 她死了
No, we won't lose her again.
不行,我们不能再失去她
Come on, help.
来啊,救命
She's not breathing.
她没有呼吸
Damn it, Brenda
可恶,布兰达
Please, damn it, please
拜托,可恶,拜托
Let me help you
让我来帮你
Charles, Charles, stop them
查理斯,查理斯,阻止他们
Stop them, stop them, what are they doing?
阻止他们,阻止他们,他们在干嘛?
Get up!
起来!
She's alive!!!
她还活着!
She's alive. Wake up
她还活着,醒来
I got it
我接到了
That's it - George
-真是够了 -乔治
The last time I try to bring anyone back from the death.
我不会再想让死人复活了
George, don't get down on yourself. I knew you were trying to help.
乔治,别气馁,我知道你是想帮忙
You are a good caring person. Which is why I like you.
你是关心别人的好人 我就喜欢你这一点
Oh, thanks Cindy, but I don't want screw your life up too
谢谢你,辛蒂 但我也不想搞砸你的人生
the most caring thing I could do for anyone right now was just get out of here.
如果我为别人着想 最好就是离开这里
George, what about Sue?
乔治,苏怎么办?
Oh yes, of course, once I get Sue, then...
哦,当然,我去找苏,然后...
Wait!
等等!
I couldn't lose a friend right now.
我现在不能再失去朋友了
Brenda's gone, Cody resents me.
布兰达走了,柯迪厌恶我
And I'm caught up in something I can't even. Oh god, it's so hard.
我非常地难过,天哪,真是辛苦
Well, you're beautiful, and your pressing up against me.
你很漂亮,你重压在我身上
Look, Cindy, I know you never considered going out with a guy like me, but...
辛蒂,我知道你没想过要和我交往 但是...
If you're not too busy tomorrow night
如果明晚你不太忙
Is that a yes?
答应了吗?
Yes.
是的
Cindy, did Brenda ever talk to you about the tape?
布兰达有跟你说过录影带的事吗?
She did mention something.
有提过一些
Do you mind if I go upstairs and look around.
介意我上楼看一下吗?
Yes, go, of course, go.
好,去吧
Cody, I will be right back, ok?
柯迪,我马上回来,行吗?
You're getting lucky tonight.
你今晚很幸运
He doesn't know you are a guy.
他不知道你是男的
Oh, Shit!
噢,糟糕!
Hello?
喂?
What? Billy May?
什么? 比利梅斯?
Who's gay? Hello
谁是同性恋? 喂
What? - Can you hear me now?
-你说什么? -你听得到吗?
Kind of - Can you hear me now?
-听得到 -你听得到吗?
Yes, perfect. - Seven days...
-好的,太好了 -七天...
Seven days? Oh my God I'm gonna die next Monday?
七天?天哪,我下星期一就要死了?
Yes, no, wait, Monday that would be seven business days, this is seven days starting now.
是的,不,等一下 是七个工作天,从现在开始算
So seven days to this very hour?
从现在开始后的七天?
My watch broke, how am I gonna know the exact hour?
我的手表坏了 要如何知道准确的时间?
Forget about hours, this day, seven days from now.
你不需要知道时间 只要记住是从现在开始后的七天
But there's a holiday coming up, do you count the holiday as a day?
但节日就快到了,节日也算一天吗?
Well that depends. What holiday?
那要看是什么节日?
Martin Luther King Day?
马丁路德国王纪念日呢?
Then no.
不行
Why not? Everybody at work is taking it off!
为什么不行?大家都放假的!
Jesus Christ, lady, I'm giving you seven frigging days.
天啊,小姐,我给你七天的时间
I could come over there and kill the shit out of you now if you'd rather have that.
你最好接受,不然我现在就去杀你
Hey, George, I don't care what you say man
嘿,乔治,我不管你怎么说
I'm signing you up with another rap battle.
我正帮你报名另一场饶舌战
Mahalik, I told you, that part of my life is over.
马哈立克,我跟你说过了 我人生的那部份已经结束了
But I said the same thing about getting the CJ's sister.
但我已经跟CJ的妹妹搞上了
But look at it, I'm still hitting it
你看看,我不是还好好的
He's still hitting it man, and she's as fine as shit That is ma sister, What?
他还好好的,而她好个屁 什么?那是...
It doesn't matter, I'm done.
已无关紧要,我收山了
So what  are you gonna do for the rest of your life, dog?
那你以后要做什么呢?
I don't know
我不知道
Yeah, yeah,  I come out
耶,耶,来啊
Maybe my brother was right, maybe I should just settle down.
也许我哥是对的,我应该安定下来
What's up then? Motherf...
搞什么? 去你妈...
I got another one.Yo
我又中一个了
Well George man, you can't focus on that shit. Let 'em go
乔治,你不能集中精神,就随它吧
You gotta try this shit George.
你试试这玩意,乔治
Yo, man, you gotta take the lid off.
兄弟,你罩子放亮点
Oh yes. - Sorry.
-妈的 -对不起
Hello?
喂?
George, something terrible happened, I really need your help.
乔治,我接到一通恐怖电话 恐怖的事发生了,我需要你的帮助
Cindy, are you ok? What's going on?
辛蒂,你没事吧? 怎么回事?
George, you have to help me, I just watched this tape the same thing that killed Brenda
乔治,你一定要帮我 我刚才看了杀布兰达的录影带
and the phone rang, and a voice said I was gonna die in 7 days.
然后电话响了,电话那头那个人说 七天内我就会死掉
Cindy, there's no such thing as a killer video tape.
辛蒂,没有这种杀人的录影带
Oh yeah, it is.
有,它就是
In fact, I know somebody who could definitely help you with that.
事实上,我知道有人可以帮你
You do, who?
真的,谁?
Wait up, I heard Joe Moore from 98 street, he watched that tape last week
等等,我听说98街的乔莫尔 他上星期看过那带子
and this morning he woke up dead. - No
-今早他醒着死了 -不
How the hell can you wake up dead?
你见鬼啦,醒着怎么死?
Cuz you were alive when you go to sleep.
因为当你去睡时是活着
Oh you just tell me you can help me - So you're telling me that you can go to bed dead and wake up alive.
-你刚刚说你可以帮我 -你说你可以睡觉时死,醒来活着
You can't go to bed dead man! That shit would be redundant
你不可能睡觉时死掉,全是屁话
Just tell me who. - No way, cuz you can go to bed and not be dead,
-告诉我是谁 -不行,因为你可以去睡觉而不死
and you can die but not be in a bed.
你可以死,但不是在床上
But you are in the bed man, that's how you wake up dead in the first place. Fool.
但你是在床上 这就是你如何醒着死的地方,笨蛋
Damn! That's some quantum shit right there - What are you talking about?
-妈的!狗屁不通 -你在说什么?
You should be takin classes, you stay dropping out
你应该上上课,免得别退学
Just tell me who can help me!!! - Damn
-告诉我,谁能帮我! -活该
My aunt Shanee ???
我阿姨夏妮能帮你
That's all it takes before you buy a new I guess you should go and see her tonight
在一切还来得及之前 你应该今晚就去看她
Tonight?
今晚吗?
But who will take care of Cody?
但谁来照顾柯迪?
George, we're gonna have so much fun .
乔治,我们会玩得很开心
I have some jigsaw puzzles, some board games,  some baseball card in my room
在我房间有一些拼图玩具 棋盘游戏、棒球卡
And a model aeroplane I'm gonna go get them   -Sure.
-还有一架飞机模型,我去拿 -好啊
OK so I made him a snack, you can give him some warm milk if he can't go to sleep.
我做了些点心给他 如果他睡不着,可以给他喝温牛奶
Don't worry, everything is gonna be fine. - Here it is.
-别担心,一切都没问题 -在这儿
I'm great with kids.
我跟孩子处得不错
Hands up, Cody.
举起手来,柯迪
Oh in case of emergency, there's a number... - I'm OK
-万一有紧急的事,有个电话... -我没事
Sorry, you're ok, kiddo?
抱歉,你没事吧?
Yeah, attaboy
好孩子
Guess that's it
大概是这个
Ok, I'm off.
我要出去了
Right.
好
I know it's funny, all the child ever really wants is a family.
我知道很可笑 我和孩子想要一个家
Yo.
我知道
Cody really likes you.
柯迪真喜欢你
Oh, he's a good kid.
他是个好孩子
Bye - Bye.
-再见 -再见
Hello?
有人在吗?
I know, you're Cindy, I'll be right with you.
我知道,你是辛蒂,我在等你来
Aunt Shaneequa?
夏妮葵阿姨?
Bingo.
答对了
But you can call me the orical. And don't worry about that vase.
你可以叫我先知 不必担心那个花瓶
What vase? Oh sorry I didn't know it, oh
什么花瓶?对不起,我不知道,喔
That vase!
那个花瓶!
Please, sit.
请坐
It was the chair.
是椅子的声音
Yes, the chair.
对,是椅子
I know why you've come.
我知道你为什么会来
A great mystery lies ahead of you
你遇到了很神秘的事情
But you must not shy away from challenge
但你不可以逃避挑战
only you can be the one who...
只有你能成为救世主...
Orpheus - What, baby?
-奥费斯 -怎样,宝贝?
Sweetie
宝贝
I'm watching the game.
看球赛
Do you mind?
你介意吗?
The Lakers will win by 12.
湖人队靠12号赢球
So can you tell me about... - the tape?
-你能告诉我关于... -录影带吗?
Yes, I watched and ... - the phone rang.
-是的,我看了... -电话就响了
Right, and then the voice say... - that you would die in 7 days.
-对,然后那声音说... -你七天内会死
Ok, that's getting... - extremely annoying.
-对,那实在... -非常讨人厌
Yes.
没错
Try being married to her, I catch shit about women I ain't even slept with yet.
我想跟她结婚 为了抓住她,我甚至不睡觉
You've made a copy of the tape, let's see it.
你做了一卷拷贝带,让我们看看
Yes, ok.
好的
Shaneequa, can you tell me if ...
夏妮葵,你能告诉我,是否...
the tape is connected to the crop circle or the aliens? Yes
-这卷带子和农作物或外星人有关? -是
But it's up to you to discover how for yourself.
那要看你自己如何去发现
Look at it's a... - Cigarette?
-你看,它是... -香烟?
I was going to say a light house.
我正要说是座灯塔
Find that light house, it's your destiny.
找到那灯塔,你的命运
Wait! What is that?
等等!那是什么?
Oh my God
天哪
There we go. Ah!
噢!
Now baby.
来打我呀
I knew that was gonna happen.
我知道会发生什么事
Ah uh, come on.
快过来
Oh hell no. get your ass.
贱女人,给我出来
What's wrong with you? Get out there
你有毛病啊?看我教训你,给我出来
Baby, no, no, let her go
宝贝,不,不,让她去吧
She spat on me, what kind of a bitch
她吐我口水,真够贱
You won, you won, you won
你赢了...
Outstay it, down low
击个掌,下面
Baby no - I'll kill her, is she crazy, is she crazy?
-别这样 -我要杀了她,她发神经啊?
What you gonna brush now? What you gonna brush now?
你现在耍什么狠? 你现在还耍什么狠?
You hit the wrong TV???
你打这台故障的电视?
George, Cody?
乔治? 柯迪?
George, what happened?
乔治,发生什么事?
I don't know, Cody and I were playing a fun game. And then I looked down, and ...
不晓得,柯迪和我在玩一个游戏 然后我看下面,就...
Yatze
就是这个
No
不
Oh my God
天哪
How could you let him watch the tape?
你怎么能让他看录影带呢?
I didn't...
我没有...
Hello
喂
It's me. How are you doing?
是我,最近好吗?
Fine.
很好
Enjoying your last week?
上礼拜过得好吗?
I can't wait to see you.
我等不及想见你
Six days now, right?
六天了,对吗?
Yeah
是的
Well, it's great catching up, can I speak to Cody?
很快就七天了 我可以和柯迪说话吗?
Why? He didn't watch the tape.!
为什么?他又没看过那录影带!
Yes, he did. Come on Cindy I do this for a living.
他看了,得了吧,辛蒂 让我跟他说话吧
Leave us alone!
离我们远点!
Hello, - I'm calling from Reader's Digest, we have a fantastic offer for Cody.
-喂 -这是读者文摘,有份礼物要给柯迪
No! you are not! You are that evil little girl from the tape.
不!你不是! 你是录影带里邪恶女孩派来的
Ok, you got me, I'd better just leave a message for him.
好吧,被你识破,那我留言给他
Fine.
好
Yeah. OK, how do you spell that? Alright, got it.
好,怎样拼?好了,我知道怎么写
Bye bye
再见
"Seven days"
"七天"
I can't believe you let that happened.
我简直不敢相信 你居然让这种事情发生了
I know, I'm sorry, I screwed up.
我知道,对不起,我把事情搞砸了
Listen, we can still save him.
听好,我们还是可以救他
The answer to the tape and your crop circles is that light house, oh, you think I'm crazy don't you?
录影带和农作物之谜的答案在灯塔 你觉得我疯了,是不是?
Of course I do. But the last thing you need now is a screw-up like me.
当然,你可别跟我一样把事情搞砸了
I'm gonna leave, for good.
我最好现在就走
Wait.
等一下
What shall I tell Cody?
我该怎么跟柯迪说?
Let him down easy. Just tell him I got call the way on business, You think of something.
让他放轻松,跟他说我有事情走了 你想个理由好了
Testicular cancer. He won't ask questions.
睾丸癌,这样他就不会问问题了
I knew you'd understand.
我就知道你够聪明
George, just be careful.
乔治,小心一点
Something weird is going on in your farm. I know it.
我知道你的农场有些诡异的事情
I don't know what you are talking about
我不懂你在说什么
sometimes the sheep just needs to be pushed through the fence.
有时候绵羊得推倒篱笆
what?
什么?
Goodbye, Cindy.
辛蒂,再见
Sue? - I can't sleep.
-苏? -我睡不着
Well, it's way past your bed time.
这是让你睡觉的方法
Won't you rock me to sleep in your big strong arms?
你不让我在你强壮的臂膀里睡吗?
There's plenty of room in the covers, it's a hot night
这里有很多房间,今晚真热
You don't need to wear pajamas.
你不需要穿睡衣
Where is my daughter?
我女儿在哪里?
Are you mad? I am your daughter.
你疯了吗?我是你女儿
No, you're not!
不,你不是!
God, come here
天啊,过来
What did you do with Sue?
你把苏怎么了?
I didn't touch her, I swear.
我没碰她,我发誓
I don't believe you.
我不相信你
Please, for god's sake, she is a girl.
拜托,她只是个女孩
You sick boy!
你这个变态!
Dad?
爸?
How do you like it? Having fun?
你喜欢这样?有趣吗?
Tom, are you...?
汤姆,是你吗...?
What in the world...? - Shh
-到底是什么...? -嘘
Look - What is that thing?
-你看 -那是什么?
I don't know.
我不知道
Maybe Cindy was right.
也许辛蒂是对的
Please, sir, all I need is 5 mins.
长官,求求你,我只需要五分钟
And I told you Campbell, no more paranoid on-air rants about the supernatural.
我告诉过你 别再报导关于超自然的东西
I know, this station is about sex violence and the weather.
我知道,这里只讲性暴力和天气
Yes, that reminds me.
对,这倒提醒我了
We're gonna need that porn star shot dead in the hurricane story, one hour.
我们需要色情明星 在暴风雨里被击毙的一小时节目
Meanwhile, a tornado in Charlston threatens the ??? beach
同时,查尔斯顿的一阵龙卷风 昨天威胁着附近的海滩
where just yesterday, a naked couple was brutally murdered.
一对裸体夫妻遭残忍谋杀
This is just 5 miles from the spot where the last couple was brutally murdered
与上一对遭谋杀夫妇的现场 只有五英哩
Turning now to sports...
现在转播体育新闻...
and an evil video tape that kills anyone who watches it in 7 days.
有一卷邪恶的录影带 任何人看了之后,七天内就会死
It's true, we are all in danger.
是真的,我们全都很危险
There is an alien force out there that tryies to prevent you from knowing the truth
有一股外星人的力量出现 想阻止你了解真相
oh Campbell, are you insane? - Trust me, it's a horrible fate. Do you hear me?
-坎波,你有毛病啊? -相信我,那是可怕的恶运,听见没?
Correction, there really is no danger, actually I didn't really mean anything I just said.
更正,真的没有危险 事实上我刚刚说的没任何意思
Yes, I did. Every word of it. Everyone watching this could be dead in a week.
对,我说了,每个字 每个看过带子的人,一周内都会死
O Shizl Gzngahr, brrttt. brrtt, btgtgtgt, Sheetn Wok Hrlry cersen blockin bracket, 123490
O SHIZL GZNGAHR BBB...@#$%^&,,1 9 3 4 19
q shnitzi guorsn blkn (,, 18 4 6 9
@#$%^& BLKN (,, 18 4 6 9
I been cleaning after this dumbass cracker Giggins for ten years,
我替那个笨蛋收拾残局十年了
but I been hittin' it with his woman for twelve.
但是我玩他的女人也有12次了
Know what I'm sayin', nigger?
黑鬼,你知道我在说什么吗?
She likes her some chocolate. Sharpton for President y'all. I'm outie.
她喜欢巧克力 现在是关于总统的新闻,我是莫迪
An evil video tape that kills people in 7 days
一卷看了七天内会死人的录影带
alien forces threatening the world, who the hell is this Cindy Campbell?
外星人力量威胁着世界 辛蒂坎波,这他妈的是谁啊?
If what she says is true, we are facing unprecedented crisis.
如果她说的是真的 我们正面临空前的危机
Get me the president
给我接总统
You are the president.
您就是总统
Good, then I already know about this.
很好,那么我已经知道了
Let's go to lunch.
我们去吃午餐吧
Sir, I think you need to go on TV
总统,我觉得您应该发表电视演说
and convice the people that there is no such thing as a UFO.
让大家相信并没有幽浮这回事
Don't spell in fornt of me, dammit.
少在我面前发号施令,妈的
Alien, sir. There's no such thing as aliens.
外星人?总统,没有外星人这回事
It's not quite true - Sir?
-这并不正确 -总统?
A year ago, a UFO crash landed in New Mexico.
一年前,一架幽浮坠落新墨西哥州
A body may have been recovered.
可能有发现一具躯体
May have been?
可能有?
Well, there was a teribble mix up.
有一个恐怖的谣传
It was thanksgiving, and the body was sent down to the kitchen
感恩节那天,尸体被送到厨房
where they stuffed stuff up to his ass, and we ate it like a state dinner
他们把他屁眼塞起来作菜吃 而我们吃得像一场国宴
That's the last I saw of it.
那是我最后一次看到它
Those scrap fat, with some sandwiches made the next day.
隔天,一些三明治夹着那些碎肉
Mr. President.
总统阁下
Listen to me carefully.
请听我说,小心点
It's ???
卡芬探员?
Back away from that window.
离窗户远一点
What, did I forget to put my pants on again?
怎么,我又忘了穿裤子吗?
No sir, it's just the feeling I been having, since the news about the aliens.
不是,自从报导有关外星人的消息 我就有种感觉
Something's not right
有些事不对劲
I know what you mean, like that feeling that something's not right.
我知道你是说那种不对劲的感觉
What is it?
那是什么感觉?
Some old 2 Pac sir.
总统,是摇滚乐
All eyes on me, hey, this shit is banging!!
所有人都在看我,真他妈的不赖耶!
Thank you sir.
谢谢夸奖
Quoddy Island Lighthouse
监狱岛灯塔
Kenosha Pierhead Lighthouse
基诺夏码头灯塔
Curlesco Island Lighthouse
克莱斯寇岛灯塔
Hello Cindy.
辛蒂,你好
I'm the Architect.
我是造物者
You have many questions.
你有许多问题
I've been watching you for a very long time.
我注意你很久了
So I see, but what's the connection between the crop circles and the video tape
我了解,农作物与录影带有何关联?
The answer is simple
答案很简单
You are the eventuality of an anomally, you are inexplicablly seeking insedulant probability
你在找一个怪异事件的最终答案 你还在找一个可能性的解决方案
Sedulant... - Grotesquely. No?
-解决方案... -荒唐地?不
What about contingent affirmation? That's gotta mean something
说是偶然事件怎么样? 那可以说明一些事
Hey, hey, you put cameras in my bath room?
喂,你把照相机放在我浴室里?
What is this? Oh my god, it was a long winter
这是什么?天啊,真是漫长的冬天
This is an invasion, ou - Sorry
-这是非法侵犯...噢 -对不起
I can't help it.
我受不了
It's very lonely in here
在这里非常孤单
Therefore I haven't been with anyone in a very long time
我很久没和任何人在一起了
not counting myself, and this chair
自己不算,还有这个椅子
I call her... Linda.
我叫她...琳达
Could you just cut the chase, i'm kind of in a rush.
你能直接说正题吗?我有急事
Why, you can always sleep over if you want
为什么?如果你想睡,随时都可以
Linda is built for two
琳达是为两个人而设计的
And she vibrates
她还能振动
Stop it, just tell me what I need to know who is that little girl?!
够了,只要告诉我那小女孩是谁?!
Okay, Okay.
好,好
My wife and I wanted a child, but she couldn't get pregnet, neither could I.
我太太和我想要一个孩子 但她和我都不孕
So you adopt it.
所以你们收养了它
We loved our daughter, but she was evil.
我们爱我们的女儿,但是她很邪恶
Made the horses crazy. Killed our puppies. Hid the remote. Really sick shit.
让马发疯、杀小动物 弄坏遥控器,真的很变态
My wife took her to the old family farm and drowned her in the well.
我太太把她带到旧农场 并将她淹死在井里
I felt a simple time-out would be sufficient.
我认为时间会冲淡一切
I tapped her and printed her evil on a video tape, I never meant to get it out, but...
我将她的邪恶录制成影带 我从没打算将它公开,可是...
but what?
可是什么?
Then I put in the wrong box and returned to BlockBuster.
那时我放错盒子,还给了百视达
Instead of my copy Pootie Tang.
代替了原来的Ａ片
It's been circulating and killing ever since.
从此就不断地流传和杀人
Just like Pootie Tang.
就像Ａ片一样
But what does it have to do with the aliens?
可是它和外星人有什么关系?
I don't know, perhaps Tabatha's summoning them to kill us all.
我不知道 也许塔贝莎召集他们要杀光我们
An alien invasion?
外星人入侵?
I have to warn the world!
我必须警告全世界!
It's already begun, you're too late.
已经开始了,太迟了
Oh my god.
噢,天哪
But not too late to make an old man happy.
能让老人家高兴,还不算太迟
What? What?!
怎么了? 怎么了?!
And now, report of lights in the sky
现在为您报导有关天空中的光柱
Glimpses of space crafts, possible alien sightings are being reported all over the world
有飞碟出现,全世界都在报导 可能是外星人来观光
Are they aliens?
他们是外星人吗?
The first video images are coming in.
第一个影像出来了
Disturbing home video tonight from a ranch outside, Sydney, Australia.
今晚这令人困惑的家庭录影 来自澳洲雪梨的一座农场
Watch very carefully now
请仔细地看
There, there, let's see that again.
那边,那边,让我们再看一遍
Very very disturbing
非常、非常令人困惑
And this is just in from Sao Paolo, Brazil.
这是刚从巴西圣保罗来的
Let's see that again.
让我们再看一遍
Very, very disturbing.
非常、非常令人困惑
And this is just in from south Texas.
这是来自德州南部的
Do they pose a threat?
他们故布疑阵吗?
Only one thing for certain.
只有一件事可以确定
We are all going to be killed.
我们都会被杀
We have to board up the house.
我们必须巩固家园
Are you sure this is necessary, Wilson?
威尔森,你确定这是必要的吗?
Having an ceremony at a time like this
在此刻办这样的典礼
Yes sir, everything must appear as business as usual
是的,所有事情都一如往常
The nation is not yet panic, it's deeply disturbed.
虽然这么令人困惑 但国家尚未陷入恐慌
Good.let's see if we could stick to that course keeping everyone deeply distrubed, who don't want to panic
很好,我不想让大家困惑却又恐慌
Very few presidents have faced a crisis like this.
没有几个总统会遇到这样的危机
I wonder what President Ford would have done?
如果是福特总统,他会怎么办?
Well, the bug stops here, the bug stops here
好啦,就谈到这里,我们开始吧
Thank you all and welcome to the White House
谢谢大家,欢迎来到白宫
The Mother Teresa Awards recognize those who have overcome the severe, handicaps and disadvantages
泰瑞莎修女奖赏那些 战胜严格考验和缺点的人
to help others and their communites
帮助他人和社会
The young, the old, black and white, our native American
不管是老的、少的 黑人、白人,还是本国人
Hey, how are you? Hey how are you, hey how are you
你好吗? 你好吗...
Well, it is therefore my honor to present each and everyone of you with this symbol of merit
我很荣幸地颁发给你们 每人一个荣誉的塑像
the room is secure, Mr. President
总统阁下,房间没问题
Or is it?!
或许吧?!
Sir?
总统?
I've been thinking Johnson, what if the aliens can take over human bodies
我有想过,詹森 假如外星人可以占据人类的身体
They look just like us, or almost?
他们看起来就像我们一样吧? 或者是差不多?
I never thought of that sir, we should be alert for anything suspicious
我从没想过那样的问题 我们应该对任何可疑的事保持警觉
It could be anywhere, even...
可能在任何地方出现,甚至...
right here!
就是这里!
My god, we never see the that coming.
天哪,我们从来没见过他们 居然就来了
It's frightening, Sir.
真可怕
Don't panic. We just move slowly, to the exit.
别慌,只要我们慢慢地走向出口
It's happening, you will never take me alive!
凑巧的,你休想抓我当活口!
She's scrambling my brain.
她叫得我快疯了
I'll get her.
我会搞定她
Good work, Sir.
干得好,总统
Good, god, the small one has metal teeth, Jerry's kids my ass
很好,有金属牙齿的小外星人 看我的厉害
Mr. President, Mr. President,  have you gone competely insane?
总统阁下,你疯了吗?
Like a fox we've got to talk to the one person Cindy Campbell
保持警觉,我们要和辛蒂坎波谈谈
She knows how to defeat the aliens. This filthy rotten scum.
她知道如何打败外星人 这些肮脏龌龊的渣子
Yeah, you hideous creature, get off my
你这丑陋的家伙,快滚
Mr. President, is everything alright?
总统阁下,没事吧?
The exits are all blocked.
出口全被堵住了
I'll find one sir
我会找到出口的
Everybody clear.
大家让开
This way, Sir.
总统,这边
God, this is insane
天啊,真是疯了
You're excited? You should feel my nipples.
很激动是吗?你应该摸摸我的奶头
Cody, Cody, Cody? Where are you?
柯迪...? 你在哪里?
Honey.
甜心
After today's incidents in the east room, the White house is advising all citizens to board up their homes
在今天白宫发生事件之后 白宫劝告所有人民要巩固家园
and prepare for an alien invasion
为了防备外星人入侵
Oh,no.
噢,不
and now, a news aid excusive
现在播报独家新闻
the killer tape you've been hearing about, we are the station that has it
您所听闻的杀人录影带 本台已独家取得
and we are showing it all night
我们将整晚播出
Very exciting, let's roll over again.
非常刺激,我们再放一遍
There, nobody gets into that side.
没人能进得来了
That's right, George. We have to get down to the cellar.
没错,乔治,我们得赶快到地下室去
George?
乔治?
Cindy
辛蒂
There's no time, get down to the cellar.
没时间了,到地下室去
Cody, God, I've been really sick about you.
-柯迪,我好挂念你 -天啊,辛蒂
He just showed up about an hour ago, I tried to call.
他大约一小时前才来的 我试着打电话给你
No, he didn't.
不,他没有打
Okay, but I was gonna.
好,但我正要打
No, he wasn't.
不,他并没有
but Cody, the point is you can't just run away like that.
柯迪,问题是你不能这么一走了之
I wanna be with George.
我想和乔治在一起
Honey, I know you want a dad, but...
甜心,我知道你想要一个爸爸 但是...
oh, trust me Cody, I'm not good at anything.
相信我,柯迪,我什么也不会
And why would i be a good dad.
没资格当个好爸爸
Uncle George.
乔治叔叔
It's gonna be ok, Cody.
会没事的,柯迪
I'm going to die, aren't I?
我就要死了,对不对?
Cody, did I ever tell you your mom said about you the day you were born?
柯迪,我有告诉过你 你妈生你那天说过的话吗?
No.
没有
I was in the delivery room with her, she was having hard time.
我和她在产房里,她生得很痛苦
And then you began to come out of her.
然后你开始冒出来
Your mom screamed and screamed in pain, she yell "just kill me bludgeon me with the bed pan".
你妈痛苦地大喊大叫 她大叫着"用尿盆杀我、打我吧"
whatever you do, put me out of this pain.
不论如何,让我脱离苦海吧
She was gushing torrents of blood.
她喷了很多血
I have all this on a tape, if you want to see it someday.
如果那天你想看的话 我有把过程录成影带
Well, finally you came out, your mom cut your umbilical cord herself.
你终于出来了 你妈亲自切掉你的肚脐
Well, on her second try.
经过两次的尝试
First time she was accidentally cut off your penis into half.
第一次的时候 她不小心把你的小弟弟切掉一半
After all she was drunk, actually drugged
毕竟是因为她醉了 事实上是嗑了药
We've been out the night before on celebrating Saint Patrick's day.
圣派屈克节前一晚,我们外出庆祝
She thought, hey, I never taste Christmas So she did just a little
她说她从没过禁药 所以她了一点
My penis?
我的小弟弟?
Yes. They sowed it on upside down
是的,他们把它弄反了
So that's why I pee up?
这就是我小便朝上的原因?
Yes, we'll get it fixed honey, it's all my list of things right after we get TiVo.
是的,在取得TiVo之后 我们就会把它修好
Anyway, there you were, your mom turned to me and she said ‘hey, you want him? Take him
总之,生了你,你妈转身跟我说 你想要他吗?带走他吧
then she died, and I took you.
然后她就死了,而我抚养了你
Do you know why?
你知道为什么吗?
I just lost my cat in a fire.
在一场火灾中,我失去了我的猫
and I need something to pet and feed
我需要饲养某些东西当作宠物
And I miss that cat Cody.
而且,我很怀念那只猫,柯迪
But I love you, nothing's ever gonna change that.
但我爱你,是不曾改变的
Not even the very painful death we're about to experience
即使是非常痛苦的死亡也不能
George!
乔治!
Are they gone?
他们走了吗?
I don't hear anything.
我什么也没听见
Don't worry Sue, it will be alright.
别担心,没问题的
It was uncle George.
是乔治叔叔
Well, scary.
哇,好吓人
Good work, Sue.
干得好,苏
I don't know what stupid idiotic thing make this light go off.
不知道什么鬼东西把灯弄灭了
Alright, there's some spare fuses in the cross bays
有一些备用的保险丝在另一间
If I can get to it,  I might get these lights back on
如果我可以拿到的话 就可以让这些灯亮起来
Quick, George, grab that rail road tie
快点,乔治,抓住那个
Damn it
噢
My balls.
我的蛋蛋
Oh, not those!
不是这个!
Jesus.
天啊
No.
不
Uncle George, I'm scaried.
乔治叔叔,我怕
Oh sweetie, come here, it's ok.
甜心,过来,没事的
There is something, on the other side of the door.
门后有东西
I can't see anything.
我什么也没看见
Oh my god.
噢,天哪
Can you see them? What are they doing?
看见他们了吗?他们到哪儿去了?
They are horrible,
太可怕了
They are greyish with big black eyes, their teeth are grotesque
他们有大而空洞的眼睛,牙齿很脏
I think they are giggling.
他们好像在笑
what?
什么?
Oh no, I think
不,我觉得他们...
Ah, help
啊,救命
Cody, oh my god.
柯迪,天哪
George, swing away.
乔治,离远点
I'm coming Cody, I will save you
我来了,柯迪,我来救你了
Die!
去死吧!
Die! Alien! Let him go!
去死吧! 外星人! 放开他!
You're not getting here  - George Bring it
-你休想把他带走 -乔治
Had enough?
可以了吗?
Forget it Cody, thank me later.
没事了,柯迪,以后再谢我
Oh Cody thank god. Come on.
噢,柯迪,感谢上帝,来
Daddy, Daddy. - Sue
-爸,爸 -苏
Mahalik, what you doing here?
马哈立克,你在这里干嘛?
Hey man, I told I will got your back.
兄弟,我说过我会罩着你的
Oh thank god, there's two of them at the door.
感谢上帝,门后头有两个
They are gone.
他们走了
Good, they couldn't get in, I hear they can't open doors.
很好,他们不能进门 我听说他们不会开门
They've mastered space flight but they can't get through wooden door?
他们精通太空飞行 却不能通过木门?
Look, the cellar is the safest place
看吧,地下室是最安全的地方
I say all the women and children stay here
所有女人和小孩们留在这儿
Boys and men, we go outside and fight.
男人到外面去作战
Right, what't the cut off age for children?
好,多大年纪算小孩?
Come on, come on.
来吧,快点
Follow me
跟我来
I'm sorry, I thought I was hitting the brake
对不起,我以为我踩了刹车
we don't have to go through insurance, do we?
我们不必通知保险公司了吧?
Mr. President, what are you doing here?
总统阁下,你在这里做什么?
I'm looking for Cindy Campbell
我在找辛蒂坎波
She may be holding the key to feeding the aliens
她可能是打败外星人的关键
Oh good, the air forces are here, with those new round planes
很好,空军和最新的飞碟来了
we don't have round plane sir.
总统,我们没有飞碟
Oh my god, oh my god.
噢,天哪...
Wait, you hear that?
等等,听见了吗?
Yo what's up George.
乔治,怎么了?
CJ
I told you I'd always got your back.
我说过我会永远罩着你的
And I got the boys
我带了一帮兄弟来
get out the car, man.
兄弟们,下车
Who we gotta shoot?
我们要射谁?
??? Let's go do this.
你们别他妈的到处乱射
You step on my shoe, bitch.
你踩到我的脚了,贱人
Call me another bitch again, and I will pop your truck. Dead in your whack
再叫我一声贱人,我就打爆你的车
Calm down, man. - Damn, homie
-冷静点 -去你妈的
In the cornfield - They're coming
-在田里 -他们来了
Don't need to worry about that, me and my boys are going to take care of this.
不用担心,我和兄弟们会搞定的
Hi, ya, come on, let's go
来,我们走
Son, I will bust this shit right now.
乖儿子,我现在就砸了这玩意
??? you're number 2 homie
我去你妈的老二
Over here, y'all
喂,这边
Get down, get down
趴下,趴下
I can't believe what i just saw.
我不敢相信我所见到的
These men died for their country
这些人为国捐躯
Send flowers to their bitches and ho's.
记得送花慰问他们的家属
I can't breath.
我不能呼吸
They must have some kind of weakness.
他们一定有什么弱点
I found it!! Without their heads, they are powerless.
我发现了!没有头,他们就没有力量
Please, no, we mean you no harm
请别这样,我们不想伤害你们
We travel to your planet to find an evil little girl
我们来地球是为了找一个小女孩
We must destroy her before 7 days.
我们必须在七天之内消灭她
You mean, you watched the video tape?
你是说,你看了那卷录影带?
Our satellite picked it up, but we thought it was Pootie Tang, that was a week ago
一周前,我们从人造卫星收看到它 我们还以为是Ａ片
And now our entire race will die, unless the girl is destroyed.
现在我们整个民族即将死亡 除非消灭这个女孩
Oh, see? They are peaceful
看到了没? 他们是爱好和平的
If they are peaceful man, why they were choking us  a few minutes ago?
如果他们是和平的人类 为什么几分钟前要掐我们脖子?
Oh, that's how we say hello.
那是我们打招呼的方式
Hello, nice to see you.
你好,很高兴见到你
Hello, Hello.
-你好 -你好
How do you guys say goodbye?
你们都怎么说再见?
I hadn't asked
当我没问
If you think that's strange, you should see how we pee.
如果你觉得那很奇怪 你应该看我们怎么小便
Ah we are not so different after all.
我们并没有很大的差别
There's something about this place, it's like i've seen this before
这个地方我似曾相识
Oh my god.
天哪
It used to be their farm.
这以前是他们的农场
She died right here.
她就死在这里
There's something down there.
下面有东西
Push back. Hey, awesome
推过去
Follow me - Yeah, you've got it
-跟我一起做 -好,你学会了
Look at this, human being and alien are working together, we all just one big XXX family
你看,人类和外星人合作 我们就像是一个大家庭
Family?
家庭?
It's just what I've been running away from
正是我所逃避的
Well, that's because you are an idiot.
那是因为你是个白痴
This is it.
就是它了
My wife took her to the old family farm and drowned her in the well.
我太太把她带到旧农场 并将她淹死在井里
The little girl, she's frightened to the well.
那小女孩害怕回到井里
Cindy!!!
辛蒂!
Time to go back down the well, bitch.
该回井里去了,贱人
Cindy!
辛蒂!
No, don't hurt him.
不,不要伤害他
Cindy, you have to come outside, the aliens...
辛蒂,你必须到外面去,外星人...
don't worry Cody, I will save you.
别担心,柯迪,我会救你的
Wait, wait
等等,等一下
Don't do this, you don't have to be evil.
不要这样,你本来不必如此邪恶
I know what happen to you, Tabatha
我知道你的遭遇,塔贝莎
I know what your mom did, that was wrong
我知道你妈做过什么,那是不对的
You were just a little girl, and you're still that little girl
你那时还是个小女孩 而现在仍然是个小女孩
just ... a lot more corpsey and with really bad teeth
只不过...看起来像僵尸 还有一口坏牙
but, maybe all you need is ... a mother
也许你需要的只是...一位母亲
and a father.
和一位父亲
We could be a family.
我们可以成为一家人
Thank you all. Your love has broken the curse and freed my soul
谢谢你们,你们的爱解开了诅咒 并释放了我的灵魂
I will never have to kill again.
我再也不必杀人了
Really?
真的吗?
No, i'm just screwing with you.
不,我是骗你们的
I just wanna tell you both good luck, we're all counting on you.
我想祝你们俩好运 我们全靠你们了
Now it's over.
终于结束了
Oh no no, it's ok, he's our friend.
不,没事的,他是我们的朋友
Thank you for saving our species, now we must return to our home planet.
谢谢你救了我们的族人 现在我们得回去我们的星球了
Goodbye then.
后会有期
Goodbye
再见
Congratulations George, you know we always got your back.
乔治,恭喜啦 我们会一直罩着你的
Just married
(新婚)
Oh, George, I'm so happy, finally we are a family.
乔治,我好高兴 我们终于是一家人了
Yeah you, me and ....damn!!
对,你、我,还有... 该死!
Cindy, George..wait.
辛蒂,乔治...等等我